[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not within the lines of the palm explored by palm readers?", "correct_answer": "Past line", "incorrect_answers": ["Life line", "Head line", "Heart line"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In geometry, which angles are called opposite?", "correct_answer": "Equal angles", "incorrect_answers": ["Angles complements of each other", "Angles reciprocals of each other", "Angles supplements of each other"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This zodiac sign is referred to as the youngest one. It is ruled by Mars and is famous as the initiator.", "correct_answer": "Aries", "incorrect_answers": ["Sagittarius", "Leo", "Taurus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is rock singer Ozzy Osbournes real name?", "correct_answer": "John Osbourne", "incorrect_answers": ["Oscilius Osbroune", "Octavius Osbourne", "James Osbourne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Feng Shui water symbolizes one of these.", "correct_answer": "Prosperity", "incorrect_answers": ["Intelligence", "Health", "Posterity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The popular casino game Blackjack is known under several different names. Which of the following is NOT one of them?", "correct_answer": "Crazy Eights", "incorrect_answers": ["Twenty-One", "Vingt-et-un", "Pontoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Ghost, Mollys hobby was sewing?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word buck is used for what male animal?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Antelope", "Deer", "Rabbit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was George and Marys last name in the movie, Its a Wonderful Life?", "correct_answer": "Bailey", "incorrect_answers": ["Clarence", "Smith", "Potter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Team America: World Police was inspired by the 1960s British television series Thunderbirds.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which U.S. state is there a region called Silver?", "correct_answer": "Texas", "incorrect_answers": ["Ohio", "Iowa", "Indiana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What job does Jake LaMotta take on after he retires from boxing?", "correct_answer": "stand up comedian and night club owner", "incorrect_answers": ["usher at a movie theatre", "bus driver", "boxing trainer"]}]